<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Themes on Brain Awareness Week</title>
    <link>http://brain.how/tags/themes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Themes on Brain Awareness Week</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brain.how/tags/themes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoints</title>
      <link>http://brain.how/materials/powerpoints/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brain.how/materials/powerpoints/</guid>
      <description> PowerPoints for Brain Awareness Week classroom presentations  Kindergarten 1st Grade 3rd Grade Version 1 3rd Grade Version 2 4-5th Grade 4-5th Grade Advanced 6th Grade 7th Grade High School Version 1 High School Version 2 High School Version 3 Animal Brains Brain Anatomy and Dysfunction Hearing Learning to Read Memory Vision  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://brain.how/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brain.how/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://brain.how/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brain.how/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>